

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Details

0968869014 benz-zy@hotmail.com

08 Nov 1994

Links

<u>facebook</u>

<u>linkin</u>

Skills

JavaScript

MySQL

HTML

React Native

Angular

Laravel

MongoDb

Nodejs

Hobbies

I love playing Moba games because it gives me the excitement of meeting great players. then want to beat them

Profile

Hi! my name is cherdpong puengtuean i am a FullStack Developer development, including design creation, coding, debugging, testing, and maintenance. Expert in devising innovative and tailored solutions to assist businesses achieve their goals in a variety of industries. Advanced skills and knowledge of leading programming tools with a strong background in mathematics, algorithms, and data-processing logic.

Employment History

Full Developer, National Telecom Public Company Limited, Bangkok

JULY 2017 - PRESENT

Database design and development of API services to connect to Web applications and Mobile applications. Technology used to develop Laravel, Nodejs for Backend. Mongodb mysql for Database React-native angular for Web Application and Mobile Application

Education

Bachelor's degree, Sripatum University, Bangkok

JUNE 2012 - JULY 2016

First class honors 3.77 GPA

EXPERIENCES

2018-2019

 Develop a Net Pracharat application for the Ministry of Digital Economy and Society, and the back-end system is PHP Laravel + Restful API. The role in this project is to provide web services to an application using PHP Laravel and Develop this application using React Native. And publish App on App Store and Play Store. This system has taken much longer because it requires training in more than 24700 villages all over the country.

2019-2020

 Develop a consumer protection management system application for the Office of the Consumer Protection Board by using PHP Laravel + VueJS.

2020-2022

- Develop an application TOTEASYLIFE new version application for Pay internet and telephone bills of TOT
- Develop an application and Digital Volunteer web application for the Ministry
 of Digital Economy and Society. The role of this position is to get the new
 project off the ground and bring the whole system up to production.

2021-2022

 Develop a system of the Ministry of Agriculture and Cooperatives for borrowing money for people using MongoDb Nodejs Angular

Project Link

Net Pracharat (Application)

Digital Volunteer (Application)

Consumer protection management system (Web Application)

TOT EASY LIFE (Application)